新疆维吾尔自治区新疆生产建设兵团，二零二四年初中学业水平考试英语试卷听力部分。
a 1. Whose scoot bag is this?
图片。理解。根据听到的句子内容，选择正确的图片。每小题读两遍。
1. Whose scoot bag is this?
2. Tom did some chores last weekend.
3. It will be cloudy tomorrow.
4. Sorry, you can't park your car here.
5. The girl plays the piano every day.
b 6. May I use your computer?
情景反应，听句子，选择正确的应答。每小题读两遍。
6. May I use your computer?
7. What about having a picnic under the tree?
8. Our class won the soccer game yesterday.
9. do you think of the story?
9. What do you think of
10. Excuse me, is there a bank near here?
c. 11. Who is that tall man in the photo?
理解.听对话及问题，选择正确的答案。每组对话读两遍。
11. Who is that tall man in the
12. Is it far from your home to school, Mike?
13. far is from Mike's home to school,
13. far is it from school,
14. does Jack like this movie?
14. I borrow this book, sir?
15. show me your card, please.
16. Where are they talking?
17. Can I borrow this book, sir?
18. show me your card, please.
19. Where are they talking?
15. Hi, Peter, have you ever been to the Great Wall?
20. I have.
I went there last year.
21. When did Peter go to the Great Wall?
短文理解，听短文，选择正确的答案。短文读两遍。
live door to an old woman.
23. She is deaf and she can't speak.
24. When we meet, she always smiles to me.
25. Her grandson lives with her.
26. He is eight years old.
27. When I take my dog, Lucky, for a walk, 28.
the boy always comes up to say hi to us.
29. One day, the boy asked me,
30. Hi, where is Lucky?
31. I answered, Oh,
Lucky is ill.
32. He is in hospital now.
33. The next day, the boy and his grandma showed up at my door.
34. They gave me a cake.
35. There was a small dog on it.
36. The boy also gave me a card.
37. It says, Get better soon, Lucky.
38. I live next door to an old woman.
39. She is deaf and she can't speak.
40. When we meet, she always smiles to me.
Her grandson lives with her.
He is eight years old.
43. When I take my dog, for a walk,
the boy always comes up to say hi to us.
45. One day, the boy asked me,
46. Hi, where is Lucky?
47. I answered, Oh, Lucky is ill.
48. He is in hospital now.
49. The next day, the boy and his grandma showed up at my door.
50. They gave me a cake.
51. There was a small dog on it.
52. The boy also gave me a card.
53. It says, Get better soon, Lucky.